Let's move ahead and turn to
our special segment, the funda of profits. Today,
our special segment is joined by
Gaurav Shah of Jeet Financial Services.
Good morning, welcome to
18 House Swadesh. First of all, best
wishes to you on Navratri. We hope
that Goddess Durga fulfills all your
wishes. Let's move ahead
and tell you the funda on stocks regarding profits in just one market.
Tell us how you are reading the market
and what would be your two strong picks.
Happy Navratri to all of you teams and viewers of the country. We pray to Mata Rani
that your wishes remain intact and you remain healthy and
happy. So, as an option, we have first chosen a non-
life general insurance company,
ICICI Lombard. This company has a
very big
market share and revenue online. We
feel that there can be a lot of improvement in the coming time.
In the last two quarters, we have
seen consistently good figures coming in and
we feel that the profits will increase further in the coming times. So,
first of all,  That option would be
Lombard for non-life general insurance and the
second option is from a public sector bank
because from the month of October, I think
your results will start coming in the second week.
Keep this person for the second time.
Different
sectors can perform very well after
opening the results. So, among public sector banks, Bank of
Baroda is where we are giving a buy opinion
and here also, if you see, there has been
continuous improvement in the last 3-4 days
and there is a 4% increase in provisioning and
many TVs are downwards. I would
like to know your quick opinion on some other spaces also because we are continuously seeing in the cement pack that
after the entry of big players, consolidation is being
expected and along with that,
in the FMCG play also, the
trigger factors that are coming for many companies FMCG are
also positive, these can be taken,
any fixed change from here
seems better than it has been for a long time and one
thing is that the biggest players have already entered
but I think a lot of loans are being taken from the government side for
Bharat Nirman. The
real estate sector is
improving.  Which is the biggest
sector regarding cement consumption i.e. consumption and there is a
big problem in private cement companies
but if I have to
name a medium sized company, mid cap cement company,
here Gayatri, which is capable
and strong, can be included and
our buy opinion is on the Government of India and
in the FMCG sector, we believe that
you will see the demand continuously improving from the big cities
but the way
Meghraj has blessed, there has been
good rain for the fourth consecutive year, India is a country,
so the demand will come back from the rural and medium rural areas as
well, so
we feel that you will see very good volume growth due to
which
you will see a good figure in profits as well and the
best thing is that the cost expenditure is gradually coming
down, so here you
can improve the margin, you are welcome to
join us to
share your stocks and to
give your own approach on the sector, so in cement pack
and fellow particular or fancy G,
ITC stock is continuously seeing shoot looks, the
stock is on the bull range of brokerage, due to that our veteran
These stocks are also included in the focus list of experts.